We have Jasmine W, comedian extraordinaire, as our headliner for the week, all right?
Because we're talking about, are there situations, are there things that you are just too old for?
Now, you already said that you're too old to be sharing a bit, sharing a room on vacay.
I get it so much. I get it.
What else? What else? Enlighten us.
Maybe we can also talk about one thing you're too old for, but that you still do.
I'm too old to be kissing everybody I go out on a date with, but I still do it.
I don't care. If you're on a date, we gon' kiss. We're definitely gonna kiss.
So I think I'm too old for that, though.
My family was like, I told my mom and my grandma, my grandma was like, uh-uh, you can't be kissing everybody.
I was like, grandma, I need to see how they kiss. I do. I gotta know.
And you know what? I've been telling people that a part of decentering men is also going with what you feel like you want to do.
It's not just about keeping your legs closed. It's also about what you want to do.
Because what do you desire? If you want to kiss somebody, kiss them.
I'm too old for trying to figure out if you like me. I'm just too old for it.
Friends, too. Friends, too.
Not just romantic. It's like, if you don't want to hang out, if you canceling, if you reschedule with me, you don't have to be my friend. It's okay.
It's so real.
We are, we are, we are.